DAWID WIŚNIEWSKI

For over 5 years I work as a programmer in the department focused on business process automation. I take part in the full path of implementation of software development projects, from presenting our achievements to potential clients, through pricing and collecting requirements, to implementation. I specialize in creating applications based on the MS Power Platform using Power Apps, Power Automate and Azure Logic Apps.



CONTACT

dawidwisniewski@outlook.com

+48 510893974

Ciołkosza 2/32, 03-134 Warsaw

in Dawid Wiśniewski

SKILLS

English

Software development

Powe Automate Power Apps Azure Logic Apps PoweShell

HTML/CSS Foreign languages



GENERAL SKILLS

Analytical thinking Problem solving Time management Teamwork Client relationship

HOBBIES

true crime literature, new technology, movies, ukulele

WORK EXPERIENCE

10/2022 - now

BlueSoft, Warsaw

Power Platform developer

- leading a team of power apps and power automate developers;
- everything listed below;

6 06/2021 - 10/2022

ISCG. Warsaw

Power Platform developer

- designing and developing projects using Microsoft Power Platform;
- debugging and supporting already deployed applications;
- development time consumption estimation;
- · writing technical documentation and user manuals

1 01/2018 - 07/2021

Geotechnology, Warsaw

Software developer

- designing new solutions;
- software development and deployment:
- debugging already created applications;
- development time consumption estimation;
- creating technical documentation of the implemented solutions
- conducting training for end-users.

6 06/2017 - 11/2017

Polfa Tarchomin S.A., Warsaw Software developer

• developing WPF application (C#, SQL Server);

12/2016 - 01/2017

Junior software developer - EDI analyst **Q** C.H. Robinson S.A., Warsaw

11/2015 - 12/2016

♀ Support Online, Warsaw

IT Consultant

EDUCATION

2012 - 2015

Military University of Technology, IT - master of science Warsaw

2007 - 2012

Military University of Technology, IT - engineer Warsaw

WORK SPREAD

